{
    "kind": "Unscramble",
    "questions": [
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "SBP5M2L6c.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the questions",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "you / Would / like / television / to / watch / ?",
                    "answer": "Would you like to watch television?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "have / you like / Would / to / soda / a / ?",
                    "answer": "Would you like to have a soda?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "a game / Would / like to / you / play / ? ",
                    "answer": "Would you like to play a game?"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "SBP5M3L13b.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the questions",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "you / written / Have / text message / ever / a /?",
                    "answer": "Have you ever written a text message?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "by ship / ever / you / Have / traveled?",
                    "answer": "Have you ever traveled by ship?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "with dolphins / Have / ever / swum / you?",
                    "answer": "Have you ever swum with dolphins?"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "SBP5M3L14a.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the sentences",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "just / He's / the towels / packed",
                    "answer": "He's just packed the towels"
                },
                {
                    "question": "found / the snorkels / just / He's ",
                    "answer": "He's just found the snorkels."
                },
                {
                    "question": "haven't / changed into / yet / We / our shorts ",
                    "answer": "We haven't changed into our shorts yet."
                },
                {
                    "question": "sunblock / hasn't / He / yet / put on",
                    "answer": "He hasn't put on sunblock yet."
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}